<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keep It Simple Stupid</title>
    <link>https://rramsden.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keep It Simple Stupid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 22:18:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rramsden.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice for the new CTO</title>
      <link>https://rramsden.ca/posts/advice-for-the-new-cto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 22:18:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rramsden.ca/posts/advice-for-the-new-cto/</guid>
      <description>Being a CTO at a small startup with 2-3 people was exciting. Titles didn&amp;rsquo;t matter, they had no weight except when pitching to investors. All that mattered back then was how fast you could put together a working prototype together.
When I was promoted to CTO at a much larger company that&amp;rsquo;s when I struggled. One of the biggest challenges was actually the title itself. In my case, I went from being a productive engineer to worrying about how others viewed me at the company and if I was living up to expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets Build a Mechanical Keyboard</title>
      <link>https://rramsden.ca/posts/lets-build-a-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 17:42:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rramsden.ca/posts/lets-build-a-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty interested in mechanical keyboards lately. Building one has been on my bucket list for awhile now so last weekend I decided to check out Yusha Kobo , a specialty keyboard store based in Tokyo which sells kits.
I purchased my first build kit the Mint60 which a split keyboard. The 60 standing for the 60% keyboard layout which is a popular form factor for hobby keyboards.
My Mint60 build kit comes with the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting for 2020</title>
      <link>https://rramsden.ca/posts/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 23:25:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rramsden.ca/posts/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>In 2013, I left Canada for a new life in Japan. I brought a laptop and a couple of pairs of clothes with me. I didn&amp;rsquo;t speak the language and had no job lined up. Because I had saved up some money, gotten my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree, and had the right work experience I was able to find a job.
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t a spontaneous decision to move to Japan. I loved Japan and had been planning most of my early 20&amp;rsquo;s on how to move there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>